London Unplugged is a drama film directed by Layke Anderson.
A portmanteau exploration of disparate characters scattered across
London, many of whose lives intersect unpredictably.
A refreshing take on the complexities, contradictions and
compromises of modern living in the greatest City on Earth.
Felix, played by Jérémy Azoulay.
Layla, played by Dimitra Barla.
David, played by Chris Barritt.
Da'nish, played by Harki Bhambra.
Marvin, played by Alexander Briem.
Jonas Andersen, played by Stephen Cavanagh.
London Unplugged is a 2018 British drama anthology film
that premiered at the East End Film Festival.
The film consists of several segments directed by numerous directors and stars Juliet
Stevenson, Poppy Miller, Imogen Stubbs, Ivanno Jeremiah, Ricky Nixon and Bruce Payne.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.